{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_4_0AMG8F",
                "player_11_0AMG8F",
                "player_9_0AMG8F",
                "player_16_0AMG8F",
                "player_7_0AMG8F",
                "player_1_0AMG8F"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                4,
                11,
                9,
                16,
                7,
                1
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "liedown",
                "liedown",
                "crouch",
                "stand",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A man with short black hair, wearing a white button-up shirt, dark pants, and black shoes. Light skin tone.",
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black fedora, black turtleneck, black pants, and black shoes.",
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes",
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    3415.932,
                    1049.812,
                    118.15,
                    0,
                    91.05991013827116,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    3237.626,
                    778.627,
                    118.15,
                    0,
                    -18.722429338368954,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    3237.712,
                    662.913,
                    118.34,
                    0,
                    -76.71627512297378,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    2732.048,
                    671.93,
                    118.34,
                    0,
                    -160.74889377407752,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    2992.895,
                    646.077,
                    118.34,
                    0,
                    -12.545446923845816,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    2959.957,
                    1523.357,
                    118.15,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            3134.675,
            761.772,
            118.34
        ],
        "sample_radius": 981.3693927004052
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            3748.175,
            460.214,
            118.34,
            0,
            146.6882354950422,
            0
        ],
        [
            2750.977,
            37.965,
            118.15,
            0,
            67.92493484676781,
            0
        ],
        [
            2611.79,
            1757.753,
            118.15,
            0,
            -60.87093639701021,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many individuals are lying motionless in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are not wearing any form of eyewear?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many men with a medium skin color are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Among all the people present, how many are women?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many figures in the scene are either crouching or holding something?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many individuals have a bald head and are also wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Excluding the individuals with light skin color, how many people are in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many men with black skin color are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. lying down"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. lying down",
                    "C. standing",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "B. lying down"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. kneeling"
                ],
                "answer": "C. lying down"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. lying down",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouching"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. kneeling"
                ],
                "answer": "B. standing"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. holding something",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "B. holding something"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            }
        }
    }
}